A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.1, Series 100 International - Series 257 Virgin Islands, U.S.A. FA386a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- South Dakota, 1936, 1939; 247; 3_Folders
  - COV-3 Covington, Platt W. "Public Health Administration In South Dakota.", 1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Tennessee, 1928-1961; 248; 2 Cubic Feet; 5 __Boxes __2 cubic feet
  Material mostly 1930's, all concerned with public health.
  248 (no program letter, general material which does not fit into a particular program area)
  248 J Public health demonstrations, local health units
  248 L Public health education (schools of hygiene and public health)
  248 Q Epidemiological investigations and studies
  248 S Social sciences
  248 T Tuberculosis
  - MIL-1 Milam, Daniel F. "Typhoid Fever In Knoxville, A Progress Report.", 1931 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Nutrition, 1949-1958 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Nutrition, 1949-1958 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Nutrition - Reports, 1942-1951; 3 Items (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Tennessee - Public Health Demonstrations, 248.J
    - TEN-1 "Full-Time County Health Work In Williamson County, Tennessee", 1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Kendrick, Joan F. - "Tennesee and Alabama, Notes on Visit To November and December 1931" (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Manual For Conduct of County Health Departments - State Department of Health - Nashville, Tennesee - MAN, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Tennessee - Public Health Education, 248.L
    - Public Health Education, 1930-1932 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Tennessee - Epidemiological Investigations and Studies, 248.Q
    - Endamoeba Histolytica - (Epidemiological Studies), 1930-1937 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Endamoeba Histolytica - (Epidemiological Studies), 1930-1937 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Endamoeba Histolytica - (Epidemiological Studies), 1930-1937 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Small Pox Vaccine Virus Study, 1932-1938 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Small Pox Vaccine Virus Study, 1932-1938 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Small Pox Vaccine Virus Study - Reports, 1934; 2 Items (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Williamson County, 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Williamson County, 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Williamson County, 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Williamson County - Report, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Tennessee - Social Sciences, 248.S
    - Fisk University, 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Fisk University - Reports, 1928-1938; 3 Items (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Fisk University - Pamphlets, Undated; 8 Items (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Tennessee - Tuberculosis, 248.T
    - PUT-2 Putnam, Persis "Tennessee - Tuberculosis Study of Pulmonary Tuberculosis Sex and Death Rates.", 1930 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Williamson County, 1930-May 1936 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Williamson County, 1930-May 1936 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Williamson County, 1930-May 1936 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Williamson County, 1930-May 1936 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Williamson County, 1930-May 1936 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Williamson County, 1930-May 1936 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Williamson County, June 1936-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Williamson County, July 1949-1961 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Williamson County, July 1949-1961 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Williamson County, July 1949-1961 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Williamson County, July 1949-1961 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Williamson County, July 1949-1961 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Williamson County - Reports, 1930-1936; 3 Items (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Williamson County - Reports, 1949-1953; 4 Items (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Williamson County - Reprints, 1938-1942; 4 Items (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Texas, 1927-1949; 249; 4 box(es)
  Mostly 1930's and 1940's. International Health Division correspondence with the State Board of Health can be found in Box 1, Folders 5-13.
  249 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings)
  249 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  249 J Public health demonstrations, local health units
  249 K Health services (epidemiology, reform, public health administration, laboratories, vital statistics, and particularly sanitary engineering)
  249 R Humanities and arts
  249 S Social sciences
  - Texas - Medical Sciences, 249.A
    - University of Texas - Sharp, William B. - (Travel, Public Health), 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Texas - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 249.D
    - University of Texas - Chemistry, 1938-1945 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - University of Texas - Chemistry, 1938-1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - University of Texas - Lwoff, Andre M. - (Refugee, Chemistry), 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Texas - Public Health Demonstrations, 249.J
    - (Public Health Demonstrations), January 1928-1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - (Public Health Demonstrations), January 1928-1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - (Public Health Demonstrations), January 1928-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - (Public Health Demonstrations), January 1928-1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - (Public Health Demonstrations), January 1928-1940 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - (Public Health Demonstrations), January 1928-1940 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - (Public Health Demonstrations), January 1928-1940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - (Public Health Demonstrations), January 1928-1940 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - (Public Health Demonstrations), January 1928-1940 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Texas - Health Services, 249.K
    - CAR-1 Carter, W. B. "Texas Statistics, Vital", 1927 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Texas - Humanities and Arts, 249.R
    - Texas Folklore Society - (Regional Studies), 1936-1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Texas Folklore Society - (Regional Studies) - Pamphlets & Reprints, 1927-1938 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - University of Texas - Broadcasting, 1938-1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - University of Texas - Broadcasting - Report, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - University of Texas - Drama, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - University of Texas - Drama, 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - University of Texas - Drama, 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - University of Texas - English Language Teaching, 1942-1944 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - University of Texas - English Language Teaching, 1942-1944 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - University of Texas - English Language Teaching - Supplementary Material, 1942-1943; 2 Items (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - University of Texas - Hispanic American Culture, 1934-1940 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - University of Texas - Hispanic American Culture, 1934-1940 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - University of Texas - Hispanic American Culture - Reprints and Pamphlets, 1932-1934; 3 Items (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - University of Texas - Latin American Drama, 1940-1948 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - University of Texas - Latin American Drama, 1940-1948 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - University of Texas - Latin American Drama, 1940-1948 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - University of Texas - Latin American Drama - Report, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - University of Texas - Latin American Studies, 1936-1949 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - University of Texas - Latin American Studies, 1936-1949 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - University of Texas - Latin American Studies, 1936-1949 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - University of Texas - Latin American Studies, 1936-1949 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - University of Texas - Latin American Studies - Reports, 1940, 1943-1944; 7 items contained in folders 36-37. (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - University of Texas - Latin American Studies - Reports, 1940, 1943-1944; 7 items contained in folders 36-37. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Texas - Social Sciences, 249.S
    - University of Texas - Social Sciences, 1932-1941 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - University of Texas - Social Sciences, 1932-1941 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - University of Texas - Social Sciences, 1932-1941 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - University of Texas - Social Sciences - Reports, 1933-1940; 7 Items (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - University of Texas - Leipziger, Hugo - (Refugee, Architecture), 1939-1942 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - University of Texas - Leipziger, Hugo - (Refugee, Architecture), 1939-1942 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - University of Texas - Leipziger, Hugo - (Refugee, Architecture) - Reprints and Pamphlets, 1940-1941; 3 Items (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Virginia, 1930-1957; 252; 4 box(es)
  Material is mostly 1930's and 1940's. Grants to the University of Virginia in a variety of fields; also local public health.
  252 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings)
  252 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  252 K Health services (epidemiology, reform, public health administration, laboratories, vital statistics, and particularly sanitary engineering)
  252 Q Epidemiological investigations and studies
  252 R Humanities and arts
  252 S Social sciences
  - Virginia - Medical Sciences, 252.A
    - University of Virginia - Maxcy, Kenneth F. - (Travel, Public Health), 1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - University of Virginia - Neale, Claude L. - (Travel, Psychiatry), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Virginia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 252.D
    - University of Virginia - Ehrenstein, Maximilian - (Refugee, Physiology Chemistry), 1934-1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - University of Virginia - Endocriniology, 1933-1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - University of Virginia - Endocriniology, 1933-1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - University of Virginia - Endocriniology - Reports, 1937-1938; 3 Items (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - University of Virginia - Natural Sciences, 1934-1941 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - University of Virginia - Physics, 1934-1935, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - University of Virginia - Physics, 1934-1935, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - University of Virginia - Ultracentrifuge, 1936-1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - University of Virginia - Ultracentrifuge, 1936-1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - University of Virginia - Ultracentrifuge, 1936-1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - University of Virginia - Ultracentrifuge, 1947-1950 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - University of Virginia - Ultracentrifuge - Reports, 1937-1940; 5 Items (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Virginia - Health Services, 252.K
    - PUT-24 Putnam, Persis "A Study of the Effect of Santitation on the Trend of Typhoid Fever and Diarrhea and Dysentary Death Rates in Selected Groups of Counties in Virginia, 1930" (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - PUT-25 Putnam, Persis "Henry County, Virginia - An Analysis of Sanitation Records", 1930 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - PUT-23 Putnam, Persis "On the Correlation Between Death Rate and Density, an Analysis of 1920 Data For 37 Counties in Virginia", 1930 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - PUT-18 Putnam, Persis "Staunton Virginia - An Analysis of Vital Statistics", 1930 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Virginia - Epidemiological Investigations and Studies, 252.Q
    - Dysentery, 1930-1938 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Dysentery, 1930-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Scarlet Fever Study, 1931-1935 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Virginia - Humanities and Arts, 252.R
    - University of Virginia - Humanities, 1934-1939, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - University of Virginia - Humanities, 1934-1939, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Virginia - Social Sciences, 252.S
    - University of Virginia - Freund, Rudolf - (Refugee, Agricultural Economics), 1938-1946 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - University of Virginia - Freund, Rudolf - (Refugee, Agricultural Economics), 1938-1946 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - University of Virginia - Freund, Rudolf - (Refugee, Agricultural Economics), 1938-1946 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences, 1930-1942, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences, 1930-1942, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences, 1930-1942, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences, 1930-1942, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences, 1930-1942, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences - Report, 1930-1940; 13 items contained in folders 32-40. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences - Report, 1930-1940; 13 items contained in folders 32-40. (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences - Report, 1930-1940; 13 items contained in folders 32-40. (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences - Report, 1930-1940; 13 items contained in folders 32-40. (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences - Report, 1930-1940; 13 items contained in folders 32-40. (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences - Report, 1930-1940; 13 items contained in folders 32-40. (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences - Report, 1930-1940; 13 items contained in folders 32-40. (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences - Report, 1930-1940; 13 items contained in folders 32-40. (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - University of Virginia - Institute for Research in the Social Sciences - Report, 1930-1940; 13 items contained in folders 32-40. (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - University of Virginia - Public Administration, 1935-1942 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - University of Virginia - Public Administration, 1935-1942 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - University of Virginia - Public Administration, 1935-1942 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - University of Virginia - Public Administration, 1935-1942 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - University of Virginia - Public Administration, 1943-1951 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - University of Virginia - Public Administration, 1943-1951 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - University of Virginia - Public Administration, 1943-1951 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - University of Virginia - Public Administration, 1943-1951 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - University of Virginia - Public Administration, 1943-1951 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - University of Virginia - Public Administration - Reports, 1935, 1937, 1939; 5 items contained in folders 50-52. (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - University of Virginia - Public Administration - Reports, 1935, 1937, 1939; 5 items contained in folders 50-52. (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - University of Virginia - Public Administration - Reports, 1935, 1937, 1939; 5 items contained in folders 50-52. (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - University of Virginia - Public Administration - Reports (News Letters), 1937-1941; 12 Items (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Washington, 1928-1971; 253; 4 box(es)
  Material is mostly 1930's and 40's; grants to the University of Washington.
  253 C Nursing (nursing education, public health nursing)
  253 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  253 R Humanities and arts
  253 S Social sciences
  - Washington - Nursing, 253.C
    - University of Washington - School of Nursing, 1930-1933 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - University of Washington - School of Nursing, 1930-1933 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - University of Washington - School of Nursing, 1930-1933 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - University of Washington - School of Nursing, 1935-1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - University of Washington - School of Nursing, 1935-1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - University of Washington - School of Nursing - Report, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - University of Washington - School of Nursing - Reports, 1937-1940; 2 Items (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - University of Washington - Oceanography, 1928-1934 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - University of Washington - Oceanography, 1928-1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - University of Washington - Oceanography, 1928-1934 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - University of Washington - Oceanography, 1928-1934 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - University of Washington - Oceanography, 1928-1934 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - University of Washington - Oceanography, 1928-1934 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Washington - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 253.D
    - University of Washington - Oceanography, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - University of Washington - Oceanography - Reports, 1928-1932; 5 Items (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - University of Washington - Thompson, Thomas C. - (Travel, Oceanography), 1930 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Washington - Humanities and Arts, 253.R
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1936-1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1936-1946 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1936-1946 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies - Report, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies - Report, 1950, 1956-1957; 3 items contained in folders 34-36. (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies - Report, 1950, 1956-1957; 3 items contained in folders 34-36. (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies - Report, 1950, 1956-1957; 3 items contained in folders 34-36. (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - University of Washington - Far Eastern Studies - Reprints, 1949-1962; 6 Items (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - University of Washington - Visiting Scholars, 1945-1948 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Washington - Social Sciences, 253.S
    - University of Washington - Mosse, Robert - (Refugee, Economics), 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - University of Washington - Mosse, Robert - (Refugee, Economics), 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Virgin Islands, U.S.A., 1932-1944; 257; 4 folder(s)
  257 I Malaria
  257 L Public Health education (schools of hygiene and public health)
  - Virgin Islands, U.S.A. - Malaria, 257.I
    - EAR-3 Earle, Walter C. and Magoon, Estus A. "St. Croix Survey, and report on Measures to Control Breeding of Anopheles", 1933 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - EAR-4 Earle, Walter C. and Magoon, Estus A. "St. Thomas Survey and report on Measures to Control Breeding of Anopheles", 1933 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - EAR-6 Magoon, Estus A. "An Inspection of Anopheles Breeding Places in the District of Coral Bay, Eastend, and Cruz Bay, on the Island of St. John of the Virgin Islands.", 1933 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Virgin Islands, U.S.A. - Public Health Education, 257.L
    - (Public Health Education) - Technician's Training Grant, 1932-1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)